[{"question":"What is Performance Testing?","answer":"Performance Testing is a type of software testing which ensures that the application is performing well under the workload. The goal of performance testing is not to find bugs but to eliminate performance bottlenecks. It measures the quality attributes of the system. ","_id":"536b4f6c-300c-4d23-94c4-e4b5c9d6d100","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"What are the different types of Performance Testing?","answer":"Load testing – It checks the application’s ability to perform under anticipated user loads. The objective is to identify performance bottlenecks before the software application goes live.\r\nStress testing – This involves testing an application under extreme workloads to see how it handles high traffic or data processing. The objective is to identify the breaking point of an application.\r\nEndurance testing – It is done to make sure the software can handle the expected load over a long period of time.\r\nSpike testing – This tests the software’s reaction to sudden large spikes in the load generated by users.\r\nVolume testing – Under Volume Testing large no. of. Data is populated in a database and the overall software system’s behavior is monitored.\r\nScalability testing – The objective of scalability testing is to determine the software application’s effectiveness in scaling up to support an increase in user load.","_id":"af9f5856-a2d3-480b-a7d8-6526c03d7e4e","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"What are the common performance problems faced by users?","answer":"Some of the common performance problems faced by users are:\r\nLonger loading time\r\nPoor response time\r\nPoor Scalability\r\nBottlenecking such as coding errors or hardware issues","_id":"338c318e-801d-43d6-b993-ffc335d75bfe","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"Name some of the common Performance Testing Tools.","answer":"The market is full of a number of tools for test management, performance testing, GUI testing, functional testing, etc. I would suggest you opt for a tool which is on-demand, easy to learn as per your skills, generic and effective for the required type of testing. Some of the common Performance Testing tools are:\r\nLoadView\r\nApache JMeter\r\nLoadUI Pro\r\nWebLoad\r\nNeoLoad","_id":"c34eddbc-f2ce-4679-9888-59ec1a36cbf9","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"List out some common Performance bottlenecks.","answer":"Some common performance bottlenecks include:\r\nCPU Utilization\r\nMemory Utilization\r\nNetworking Utilization\r\nS limitation\r\nDisk Usage","_id":"3f956b74-1647-402f-b712-a3a4a5826e18","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"What are the Parameters considered for Performance Testing?","answer":"The Parameters for Performance Testing are:\r\nMemory usage\r\nProcessor usage\r\nBandwidth\r\nMemory pages\r\nNetwork output queue length\r\nResponse time\r\nCPU interruption per second\r\nCommitted memory\r\nThread counts\r\nTop waits","_id":"c6180f83-24ad-462f-9b63-a4dd9d0661ca","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"What is throughput in Performance Testing?","answer":"Throughput is referred to the amount of data transported to the server in responds to the client request at a given period of time. It is calculated in terms of requests per second, calls per day, reports per year, hits per second, etc. Performance of application depends on throughput value, higher the value of throughput -higher the performance of the application.","_id":"dc139d5e-3f7d-467b-b0e9-2accff59c165","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"What is Endurance Testing & Spike Testing?","answer":"Endurance Testing – It is a type of performance testing where the testing is conducted to evaluate the behavior of the system when a significant workload is given continuously.\r\nSpike Testing – It is a type of performance testing that is performed to analyze the behavior of the system when the load is increased substantially.","_id":"d6521862-5161-459f-b207-b4f83cc467c9","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"What are the different phases for automated Performance Testing?","answer":"Design or Planning\r\nBuild\r\nExecution\r\nAnalyzing & Tuning","_id":"438ca10a-017a-4413-8d81-8ec6d3d1965b","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"What is a Protocol? Name some Protocols.","answer":"A protocol is a defined as a set of various rules for the purpose of information communication between the two or more systems.\r\nSome of the Protocols are :\r\nHTTP\r\nHTTPS\r\nFTP\r\nWeb Services\r\nCitrix","_id":"64d46fdf-4aac-4a87-b477-1f8c4e75258f","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"},{"question":"What is a Performance Tuning?","answer":"Performance tuning is the improvement of system performance. Typically in computer systems, the motivation for such activity is called a performance problem. It can be either real or anticipated and most systems will respond to increased load with some degree of decreasing performance.","_id":"aee22fcc-f206-4800-b457-429d06174842","categoryId":"84001edd-07d4-42a9-ba9d-84a89482c188"}]